Norbertas Lapenas

Mobile: 085 114-9751

Email: nlapenas@gmail.com

Website: https://norbertasl.github.io/ GitHub: https://github.com/Norbertasl 27 The Meadows, Oldgrange Wood, Monasterevin, Co.Kildare.

Key Characteristics

Professional, hard working and motivated individual who is very enthusiastic in starting software development work. I have experience of working in a variety of roles including as a construction operative, window and door installer, delicatessen assistant and as an environmental worker

I have excellent problem solving, technical, customer service, communication, IT, programming, planning and organisational skills. I have undertaken continuous study throughout my working career to ensure my skills and qualifications are relevant. I am versatile and, as shown below, adapt to new roles and challenges easily. I have excellent team working skills with experience of working in fast paced environments.

Professional Qualifications

2019 Full Stack Developer Course – On-line with Code Institute

2019 County Kildare Leader Partnership, Jigginstown, Naas, Co Kildare

Business Development Course

Marketing QQI Level 5

2016 Java SE 8 Associate Programmer Certificate

2010 Moyle Park College, Clondalkin, Dublin

Junior and Leaving Certificates completed. Best student awards in 3rd and 5th year.

Front End Skills

Back End Skills:

HTML / HTML5	Java / Spring
 CSS / CCS3 / Bootstrap 	Python / Django
JavaScript / jQuery / AngularJS	SQL / noSQL
Responsive Design	REST API

General Skills:

Version Control /Git	Team Player
Problem Solver	 Dedication to knowledge
Self-Motivated/Self Driven	Excellent communication skills

Career Summary

2010-2019 A Gilligan Builders, Ballymount Drive, Ballymount, Dublin 12

Role Construction Operative/Installer

This was a full time and part-time role since 2010. I had a wide range of duties and responsibilities which made me a really fast learner and improved my communication skills. One key duty for me was to reassure the customers about the work that was being performed and explaining the next steps we will be undertaking.

2017-2018 Brendan McGee Construction, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

Role Construction Operative

This was a short-term role in a very fast pace building site environment. My roles involved making sure we prioritized the correct work and that every-one was clear on the projects that needed to be done.

2015-2017 Junction 14 Service Station, Monasterevin, Co Kildare

Role Delicatessen Assistant

My key role was working in the front of the house of the deli section and to serve customers. It was a very busy environment, so efficiency was key. When we did not have a lot of customers I would go into the back and help out in the kitchen and preparation stations. It was a very team oriented work experience for me and it taught me a lot about respecting other people work and if possible helping them out when they are struggling.

2014-2015 Oxigen Environmental, Naas, Co Kildare

Role Environmental Refuse Collector

I worked as part of a team of environmental refuse collectors providing a refuse collection service to customers throughout county Kildare.

References available on request.

Interests

- 3D Printing(I assembled my own in 2018)
- Motorbike and driving on the country roads
- Mixed Martial Arts BJJ
- Cycling Cycled from Netherlands to France just for the fun of it.